Not brothers, Delta is here to give Big Red and Jinpi for free again. This Treasure Month event,
I always give two gold skins first. Just choose six from the nine guns on the ground.
Is there any brother who can practice all these guns? Then there are a lot of storms and Baksijinet,
Twelve new treasure chests have been added. As long as you open the treasure map with the corresponding number, you can get the treasure.
Of course the treasures are all kinds of Big Red. First grab the store, but unfortunately Xiahong has them all.
Upgrades include inner tanks of ten thousand gold and rocket fuel, specialties of the imperial capital.
For those who don’t want to go to Space Bakshiai to make souvenirs, this opportunity has come.
There are two ways to obtain the treasure map: the first is to touch a specific container to get it;
The second is that the invading Hafk team has a chance of exploding.
Then brothers, you must remember that the most precious of all treasure maps is No. 8.
Just follow the official screen. Xiao Pu boldly speculated that the items given by Treasure No. 8 were all big monkeys.
There may even be a rare giant monkey exclusive to this event.
Treasure No. 8 on the three maps is located near the medical pile in the dam container.
The long-term workers rescued the burning mountain next to it,
Near the high platform of Bakexi Babie Tower or the top-floor swimming pool. Brothers who want big monkeys,
When the time comes to get the gambler, you don’t need me to teach you, right? Never mind,
I have to prepare the dream of tomorrow and treasure chest No. 8.